Guide to the the Richard W. Lyman, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0215
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Series 1
  - Jordan, David Starr, Scholarship, 1958-66 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Klein, Margaret Galimore, and William Klein Scholarship, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - National Merit Scholarships, 1965-70 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Richards, Mabel Wilson, Scholarship Fund, 1969-70 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Scott Paper Co. Scholarship (Award), 1955-69 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Sloan, Alfred P., National Scholarships, 1954-69 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Sloss, Leon, Scholarship, 1922-62 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Sloss, Louis'and Sarah, Scholarship, 1934-58 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Stanford, Leland Jr., Memorial Scholarship, 1919-61 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Terman, Frederick B., Scholarship Fund, 1943-66 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, Scholarship, 1943-56 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Assistant to the President. Inquiries and/or notice of search, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Assistant to the President. Letters providing names and information, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Assistant to the President. No thank you letters, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Abeyta, Victor, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Acevedo, Jorge, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Aragón, John W., 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Arredondo, Hank, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Banda, Manuel, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Bayonda, Hugo, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Camacho, Victor, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Campa, Arthur L., 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Cancino, F.C, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Carrasco, David L, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Chacon, Jose (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Chavez, J. Gilbert (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Elizondo, Sergio, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Flores, Genaro, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Gallegos, A. Moses, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Gallegos, Gene, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Garza, de la Rodolfo, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Hernandez, Raul J, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Jaramillo, Raul, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Kaslow, Audrey A, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Martinez, Gilbert, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Mercure, Alex P, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Morendo, J. Hector, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Nortenson, Ben F, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Orozco, Cecil, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Paramo, Ernest J, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Pena, Hiario S, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Ramirez, Oscar 5, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Reyna, Henry, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Rivers, Carlos, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Salamanca, Anthony, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Tellez, Thomas, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Terrones, Edward, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Torres, Andy R, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Velarde, Vidal, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Valencia, Atilano, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Villanveva, Louis, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Zazveta, Richard, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Cabrera, Richard, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Gutierrez, Felix, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Calderón, Richard, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Juárez, Jose, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Samoya, Julian (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Telles, Raymond (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Lopez, Henry P, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Almanzan, Robert, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Bertoglio, Joseph, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Borrego, Eva, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Cabrero, Arturo, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Camacho, Joseph, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Carrillo, George, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Flores, Luis, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Flores, Salvador, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Gonzalez, Simón, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Leyba, Charles, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - López, Ronald, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - Manriquez, Napoleón, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - Morales, Hilbert., 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - Ortega, Rudy, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - Romo, John, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - Roybal, Thos. De A, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - Rubalcava, Roberta, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  - Sanchez, David, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - Sanchez, Pedro, 1969-70 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - Search Committee Assistant to President. Interviews, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - Replies (concerning above), 1968 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - Coordinator of Inter-Group Relations, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  - CIR: General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 71)
  - CIR: Job Description, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 72)
  - [CIR: Replies.], 1968 (Box 37, Folder 73)
  - CIR: Request for names, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 74)
  - CIR: Sample Letters (Box 37, Folder 75)
  - CIR: Henry Anderson, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 76)
  - Horace Anderson (Box 37, Folder 77)
  - James Banks (Box 37, Folder 78)
  - William C. Barnes (Box 37, Folder 79)
  - Albert Barringer (Box 37, Folder 80)
  - Joseph F. Brooks (Box 37, Folder 81)
  - Roscoe Brown (Box 37, Folder 82)
  - John D. Butler (Box 37, Folder 83)
  - Paul Chann (Box 37, Folder 84)
  - Evelyn Clark (Box 37, Folder 85)
  - Noyes Collinson (Box 37, Folder 86)
  - James Crawford (Box 37, Folder 87)
  - Zelte Crawford (Box 37, Folder 88)
  - Fredrich Drayton (Box 37, Folder 89)
  - Felix Elizalde (Box 37, Folder 90)
  - James Forrest (Box 37, Folder 91)
  - Kenneth C. Goode (Box 37, Folder 92)
  - John Henderson (Box 37, Folder 93)
  - Robert Hoover (Box 37, Folder 94)
  - Robert W. Lawrence (Box 37, Folder 95)
  - Ennis McDaniel (Box 37, Folder 96)
  - Jerome Miller (Box 37, Folder 97)
  - Arthur Milton (Box 37, Folder 98)
  - Charles Modiste (Box 37, Folder 99)
  - William Moses (Box 37, Folder 100)
  - James Moses, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 101)
  - Henry Organ. (empty) (Box 37, Folder 102)
  - Ernestine Patterson (Box 37, Folder 103)
  - Anthony Rachal, Jr (Box 37, Folder 104)
  - Peter Robinson (Box 37, Folder 105)
  - Nancy Roche (Box 37, Folder 106)
  - Alan Rogers (Box 37, Folder 107)
  - Pedro Sanchez (Box 37, Folder 108)
  - Franklin Sands (Box 37, Folder 109)
  - Edward C. Sylvester, Jr (Box 37, Folder 110)
  - William Trueheart (Box 37, Folder 111)
  - Charles Wade (Box 37, Folder 112)
  - JoAnne Walker (Box 37, Folder 113)
  - John Walker (Box 37, Folder 114)
  - Thomas C. Walker (Box 37, Folder 115)
  - Sidney Walton (Box 37, Folder 116)
  - Tom Williams (Box 37, Folder 117)
  - Dr. Charles Wilson (Box 37, Folder 118)
  - Departments (suggestions and miscellany), 1966-69 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Data Processing, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Admissions (minority), 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Funding for minority programs, 1968-69 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - As pertains to Mexican-American admissions. (minority), 1969 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Pilot program (admissions experiment) - see: Ford Grant. Admissions (general), 1967-70 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Information given to Stanford applicants, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Admissions, future, 1965-70 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Admissions cases, 1970-71 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Admissions. A-Z, 1970-71 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Admissions, (freshmen), 1969-70 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Admissions, 1969-70 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Admissions, transfer, 1969-70 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Aeronautics and astronautics, School of Engineering, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Aerospace Studies. (Air Force), 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Implementation of new requirement (no degree credit given for military-taught or AFROTC courses) 1969 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - African and Afro-American studies, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Anatomy, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Anthropology. Departmental visitation team for the Dept. of Anthropology, see: Graduate Education Study Committee, 1965-70 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Applied behavioral sciences, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Applied mathematics and statistics laboratory, 1958-61 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Applied physics, 1963-69 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Architectural Advisory Council, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Archives, 1963-69 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Art Gallery and Museum, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Asian Languages, 1966-69 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Bechtel International Center, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Biochemistry, 1966-70 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Biological Sciences. See also: Committee on Financial Awards, 1966-70 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Business, Graduate School of, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Re: Fund raising for GSB, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Minority programs at GSB, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Business office and business affairs, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Business, Graduate School of, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Business School Advisory Council, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Dean, Graduate School of Business, 1969-70 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Business School Affiliates Program, 1967-70 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Business Development Association, Graduate School of Business, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Business Placement Office, Graduate School of Business, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - International Center for the Advancement of Management Education - Graduate School of Business, 1967-69 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Career planning and placement center, 1968-72 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Chancellor's Office, 1967-70 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Chemistry, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Classics, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Communication, 1967-70 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Community and preventive medicine, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Comparative literature, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Computation Center, 1966-70 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - matter of idle computer time/arrangements for external computing services or equipment, 1960-68 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Development, Vice-President for, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - Earth Sciences visiting committee, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - East Asian Studies, Center for, 1969-70 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Economics, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - Education department, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - Center for research and development in teaching - Education, 1969-70 (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - Education, visiting committee, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 57)
  - [Engineering] School of Engineering Advisory Council, 1969-70 (Box 38, Folder 58)
  - Advisory Council, Engineering School, 1969-70 (Box 38, Folder 59)
  - [Engineering] Bio-medical engineering, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 60)
  - [Engineering] Mineral Engineering (re-named Applied Earth Sciences), 1969 (Box 38, Folder 61)
  - Financial Aids, 1965-70 (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - College work study program, 1966-70 (Box 38, Folder 63)
  - Educational opportunities grant, financial aids, 1965-70 (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - Food Research Institute. (empty) (Box 38, Folder 65)
  - Foreign Student Advisor's Office, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 66)
  - French and Italian, 1965-70 (Box 38, Folder 67)
  - Leonardo da Vinci Society, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 68)
  - General Secretary's Office, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 69)
  - General Studies, 1967-69 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - Geology, 1967-70 (Box 38, Folder 71)
  - Geophysics, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 72)
  - German Studies, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 73)
  - Graduate Division, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 74)
  - Hansen Laboratories, 1967-70 (Box 38, Folder 75)
  - Health Service, 1948-69 (Box 38, Folder 76)
  - Immunization/Health service requirements/exceptions (Box 38, Folder 77)
  - re: contraceptives, 1962-70 (Box 38, Folder 78)
  - re: contraceptives - Health Service. Complaints and commendations, 1969-70 (Box 38, Folder 79)
  - History, 1968-70 (Box 38, Folder 80)
  - Hoover Institution. [file out], 1969-70 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Institution (challenge from Libertarians and others). [file out], 1969 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Proposal to the Dept. of Defense for research on sources of threats to the U.S. from international communists. [file out], 1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Committee to screen research proposals from Hoover Institution (Brooks, Cilley, Campbell). [file out], 1969 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Glenn Campbell. [file out], 1968 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Hoover Institution. Senior fellows, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Hoover Tower security, 1950-68 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 1966-68 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Housing Office, 1968-70 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Human Development / Biology, 1969-70 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Humanities and Sciences, 1968-70 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Humanities, Honors programs, 1960-69 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Humanities - Special Programs, 1967-69 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Religious studies, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Institute of political Studies, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Insurance, Safety and Health Physics, 1969-70 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Latin American Studies, Center for, 1967-70 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Law School, 1965-69 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Libraries, University, 1966-70 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Main Library Development Plan, 1962-70 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Materials Research, Center for, 1961-68 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Mathematics, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Medicine, 1967-70 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - [Medicine, School of] Coordinating Council of the Professional Women of Stanford Medical School, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - [Memorial Church], Dean of the Chapel, 1965-69 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - [Memorial Church], University Chaplain, 1967-69 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Military Science, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Stanford United Ministry, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Multi-disciplinary Health Services Research, Provisional Program in, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Nursing, School of, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Nursing School Accreditation, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Overseas Campus Program / Policies, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Stanford in France, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Stanford in Germany, 1957-70 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Leverhulme Graduate Overseas Program, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Stanford in Italy, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Stanford in Mexico, 1969-70 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Proposal for cooperation between the Centre International de Formation Europeane and Stanford and other institutions, 1966-70 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Intercollegiate Center for Classical Studies in Rome, 1968-69 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Stanford in Spain, 1968-69 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Inter-University Program for language studies in Taipei, 1965-66 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Center for Japanese Studies in Tokyo, 1964-65 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Operations Research, 1968-70 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Patent Administration, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Personnel and Employee Relations, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Petroleum Engineering, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Pharmacology, 1969-70 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Philosophy, 1967-69 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, 1967-69 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - [Physical Education and Athletics] (cont'd) (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - Search for full-time supervisor of officials (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - stunts: Leaflet flights, propaganda, advertising, card stunts, [1965] (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Basketball; baseball; soccer, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Academic background / statistics re: Stanford athletes, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Coaching P.E. Department, 1967-69 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - Council of Athletes, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - Discrimination in athletics. P.E. Department, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - discrimination in athletics (other universities), 1970 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - East-West game and brunch, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - Faculty athletic representatives, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Football, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Press box / general information, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - Football tickets, 1967-70 (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - Athletic Department master plan, 1968-69 (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - Athletic Phase II building project, 1968-69 (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - Physical Education, Women, 1968-70 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  - Physical plant (name changed to Plant Services, 1971-72), 1969-70 (Box 39, Folder 67)
  - layoff begins of university painters and carpenters, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 68)
  - Physics. see also: Biological Sciences for Biophysics Dept, 1967-70 (Box 39, Folder 69)
  - Planning, 1968-70; AD 12.14.7/29 (Box 39, Folder 70)
  - Architectural selection Committee Planning (auxiliary file) (Box 39, Folder 71)
  - Police Department, 1967-70 (Box 39, Folder 72)
  - Board action re: Police Dept. / Police powers, etc, 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 72)
  - Police reports, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 73)
  - Issue of increased Police protection / Safety on campus, 1969-70 (Box 39, Folder 74)
  - Political Science, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 75)
  - President's Office (Box 39, Folder 76)
  - Security Measure in the President's Office, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 77)
  - Assistant to the President for Mexican Affairs - Luis Nagales, 1969-70; AD4.17 (Box 39, Folder 78)
  - Simmons, Assistant to the President, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 79)
  - Academic Secretary, President's Office, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 80)
  - Legal Advisor to the President, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 81)
  - Assistant to the President - Southern Ca1ifornia, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 82)
  - Press, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 83)
  - Psychiatry Dept, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 84)
  - Psychology, 1968-69 (Box 39, Folder 85)
  - Public Events, 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 86)
  - Academic Gowns. Public Events, 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 87)
  - Public Safety, Director of, 1968-69 (Box 39, Folder 88)
  - Publications Service, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 89)
  - purchasing, 1962-71 (Box 39, Folder 90)
  - Registrar, 1967-69 (Box 39, Folder 91)
  - Religious Studies. see: Special Program in Humanities, Stanford United Ministry, Religious movement (in General file for student attitudes.) (Box 39, Folder 92)
  - Research, Vice-President for, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 93)
  - Research Administration, 1968-69 (Box 39, Folder 94)
  - Research Information Center, 1969-70 (Box 39, Folder 95)
  - Residence Halls / Food Services, 1963-68 (Box 39, Folder 96)
  - Guests in Residence, 1963-68 (Box 39, Folder 97)
  - Stern Guest-in-residence, 1963-68 (Box 39, Folder 98)
  - Russian and East European Studies, Center for, 1967-69 (Box 39, Folder 99)
  - Safety, Insurance and Health, 1967-70 (Box 39, Folder 100)
  - Slavic, 1968-69 (Box 39, Folder 101)
  - Sociology, 1968-69 (Box 39, Folder 102)
  - Spanish and Portuguese, 1968-70 (Box 39, Folder 103)
  - Speech and drama, see: Drama dept (Box 39, Folder 104)
  - Statistics, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 105)
  - Student Counseling Services, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 106)
  - Systematic Biology, Division of, 1968-71 (Box 39, Folder 107)
  - Tresidder Union, 1966-69 (Box 39, Folder 108)
  - Tresidder Union - Liberation, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 109)
  - Committees (general) Chairman/responsibilities/membership criteria, 1969-71 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Decorum during meetings, etc. Committees (general), 1966-69 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Faculty / Jr. faculty representation on committees, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council (correspondence), 1964-71 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Criteria for membership to the academic council, 1969-71 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council, Conference committee, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Academic Council, Memorial and other resolutions, 1968-70 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Academic Council, Steering Committee, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Advising and individual student petitions, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Academic Senate (general correspondence.), 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - constituency meetings, 1970-71 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - charge and membership-see: Ad hoc Committee on revision of Senate rules (for old working papers re: rules of Senate), 1968-70 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Advisory Board, 1968-70 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Committee membership/procedures, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Ad hoc Subcommittee on the Advisory Board to prepare recommendations for by-laws in elections., 1969 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - University Advisory Committee, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Function / membership, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Procedure to obtain hearings at BIT, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Presidential Commission on external Affirmative Action, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Advisory committee on external Affirmative Action-charge and membership, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Committee on African and Afro-American Studies, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Ad hoc Committee on Architecture (Provost's), 1967-69 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Archives advisory council, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - President's advisory committee on the Art Gallery and Museum, 1962-64 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Committee on acceptance or rejection of art objects, 1958-68 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Awards, Prizes and Honors, 1969-71 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Behavioral and social sciences survey committee, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - University budget committee, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Commission on use of biocides. see: Committee on Health and safety (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Advisory committee on the, university budget adjustment program [BAP], 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Committee on business and financial operations, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Committee to review and aid in decisions of the business office, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Ad hoc committee on the Academic calendar, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Committee of Fifteen., 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Committee on Committees, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - committee structure, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Committee on Comparative literature, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Community Health Planning Committee, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Committee on community medicine, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - President's advisory committee on non-faculty compensation, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Ad hoc committee on course credit and requirements, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Committee on SUSE Futures. (School of Education), 1971 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Educational inquiry committee. Quarter vs. semester system, 1955-69 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - interim report of the semester and quarter systems, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Enrollment policies committee. Graduate division, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Committee on computation facilities, 1969-71 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Articles of organization of the faculty, 1958-64 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - AAUP Committee on faculty benefits, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Faculty consultative group on campus disruptions, 1968-70 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - membership and charge, 1968-70 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - emergency procedures, committee on disruptions, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Committee on the faculty handbook, 1970-71 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Ad hoc faculty information committee, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Fall-out shelter - Civil defense committee, 1968-69 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Fall-out shelter - Civil defense committee, 1968-70 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Financial awards (external). see also following files for Rhodes, Fulbright, etc, 1965-71 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Churchill Scholarship, 1967-68 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Fulbright Scholarship Committee, 1967-69 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Rhodes - Marshall Scholarship Committee, 1966-70 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Floor management Committee. See: Faculty self-discipline committee (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Ad hoc committee on long range financial planning. see also: Advisory Committee on university budget, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Ad hoc Food review committee, 1968-70 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Committee on Foreign Study Programs, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - membership and charge, 1969-70 (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Sub-committees, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Planning Committee for freshman registration, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Ad hoc committee to plan a major fund raising campaign (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - Committee on governing the university. AAUP, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 68)